photoblogs.com 2011-11-11

# Privacy Policy - Photoblogs.com

## Privacy Policy

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails   
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

### How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

### Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Email [support@photoblogs.com](mailto:support@photoblogs.com) or use our [contact page](http://www.photoblogs.com/contact)
